♪♪
- All right, Dawn. This is your chance
to take the Fantasy Fashion lead.
- You're going down, Mae.
Hit me with a scenario.
- Okay.
Find the perfect outfit for a group hang
that includes a boy you like who's really sweet
and loves cupcakes even though his mom is a dentist.
[laughter]
- Really?
真的吗？
- What?
什么？
- You just want me to pick out an outfit
你只是想让我帮你挑一套衣服
for the next time you see Miles.
下次见Miles的时候穿。
- [scoffs] You're on the clock, go!
（嗤之以鼻）你计时开始了，快点！
[laughter]
（笑声）
- Uh...
呃...
Oh! Pink and westerny?
哦！粉色和西部风格？
- Pink, yes.
粉色，是的。
Westerny? Aw, heck no.
西部风格？哦，算了吧。
- [groans]
- [呻吟]
Just tell me what Miles likes.
告诉我Miles喜欢什么。
- You're running out of time. - Stop pressuring me!
- 你时间不多了。 - 别给我压力！
- That's the game!
- 这就是游戏规则！
- We're running out of time!
- 我们时间不多了！
- Stop pressuring me. - That's the game.
- 别给我压力。 - 这就是游戏规则。
- The Quad Squadron is supposed to be a team.
- 四方小队应该是团队。
- You're right. Now get in formation,
- 你说得对。现在进入队形，
and let's finish off that helicarrier!
让我们干掉那架直升机！
[all yelling]
[众人喊叫]
- All that noise for a stupid video game?
- 为了一个愚蠢的视频游戏吵成这样？
I just don't get boys sometimes.
我有时候就是搞不懂男孩子们。
- [groans] Where is my pink skirt?
- [叹气] 我的粉色裙子在哪儿？
Ugh!
呃！
- All that noise for a stupid fashion game?
- 为了一个愚蠢的时尚游戏吵成这样？
I just don't get girls sometimes.
我有时候就是搞不懂女孩子们。
Bogey on your six!
敌机在你六点钟方向！
[video game sounds]
[电子游戏音效]
- Ugh! I can't concentrate with that noise!
- 呃！这种噪音我怎么集中注意力！
[video game sounds]
[电子游戏音效]
[music volume increases]
[音乐音量增加]
- Keep it down up there!
- 上面小声点！
- Keep it down, down there!
- 下面小声点！
[video game sounds]
[电子游戏声音]
[banging]
[敲击声]
all: Keep it down!
所有人: 小声点！
[video game sounds]
[电子游戏声音]
[electronic music]
[电子音乐]
[laughter]
[笑声]
all: What did you do?
所有人: 你们做了什么？
[laughter]
笑声
[upbeat music]
轻快的音乐
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪
[whistling]
口哨声
♪ ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪
♪ One, two ♪ - ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
♪ 一，二 ♪ - ♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪
- ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
- ♪ 一，二，三，四！♪
♪
- Whoa!
- 哇！
- Mom's gonna beat your high score.
妈妈要打破你的高分记录了。
- Oh, I'm not worried.
哦，我不担心。
It's called the Papa Tom Shot for a reason.
这招叫爸爸汤姆投篮是有原因的。
[laughter]
[笑声]
- 'Cause Mama hadn't shot on it yet?
因为妈妈还没投过？
[laughter]
[笑声]
- [mimicking] Because Mama hadn't shot on it.
[模仿]因为妈妈还没投过。
[murmuring]
[低语]
[laughter]
[笑声]
- Hey, Mae!
嘿，梅！
Ready for a little Friday dine and dish?
准备好享受一个周五的晚餐和闲聊了吗？
- Yeah, sorry our "Movie Monday"
是的，抱歉我们的“电影星期一”
and our "Just the Two of Us Tuesday"
和我们的“只有我们俩的星期二”
kind of became group hangs with Miles.
有点变成了和Miles的集体聚会。
- Hey, it's all good, Mae.
嘿，没关系，Mae。
Okay, now let's get into the dishing.
好了，现在让我们开始闲聊吧。
Okay, so in the middle of math class, Riley said she wanted--
好的，所以在数学课中间，Riley说她想要——
- Hey, girl!
嘿，女孩！
- Sorry, that's my text chime for Miles.
抱歉，那是Miles的短信提示音。
[laughing]
（笑）
He's so funny.
他太有趣了。
- [chuckles] What'd he say?
——[轻笑]他说了什么？
- He said, "Hi."
——他说：“嗨。”
[laughter]
[笑声]
- You had to be there. [chuckles]
——你得在场才能懂。[轻笑]
- I am here.
——我在这里。
[laughter]
[笑声]
Okay, anyway, in the middle of math class,
好吧，不管怎样，在数学课中间，
- Hey, girl!
——嘿，女孩！
- Keep going, I won't check it.
——继续，我不会查看的。
- Riley said-- - Hey, girl!
- 莱利说——嘿，女孩！
- That she wanted-- - Hey, girl!
- 她说她想要——嘿，女孩！
- Wanted to-- - Hey, girl!
- 想要——嘿，女孩！
- Please check it!
- 请检查一下！
- No, I'll silence it.
- 不，我会静音的。
- So she said that she--
- 所以她说她——
- Hey, girl!
- 嘿，女孩！
[laughter]
[笑声]
- Oh.
- 哦。
- Don't worry, Dawn. He doesn't have to sit with us.
- 别担心，Dawn。他不必和我们坐在一起。
- No, it's--it's cool, we can make it a group hang.
不，没事，我们可以搞个集体活动。
Again.
再来一次。
- Great!
太好了！
- Hey! - Hey!
嘿！
- Hey!
Okay, now that we're all hey'd up,
嘿！
back to dishin'.
好了，我们都打过招呼了，
Okay, so in the middle of math class, Riley--
继续八卦。
[both giggling]
好的，所以在数学课中间，Riley——
Stood on her desk and burped the "Star Spangled Banner."
站在桌子上，用嗝声唱了‘星条旗’。
[laughter]
[笑声]
In Portuguese!
用葡萄牙语！
While...
同时...
juggling three kittens.
抛接三只小猫。
[chuckles]
[轻笑]
♪ Meow, meow, meow, me-meow, meow, meow, meow ♪
♪喵，喵，喵，喵-喵，喵，喵，喵♪
[chuckles]
[轻笑]
Me-out!
喵-出去了！
[laughter]
[笑声]
[machine dinging]
[机器叮咚声]
Hey, Dad, what's wrong?
嘿，爸爸，怎么了？
- Oh, nothing, nothing. What's uh...
哦，没事，没事。你...你...
what's wrong with you?
你怎么了？
- Nothing...
没事...
Mae keeps blowing me off for Miles!
Mae总是为了Miles拒绝我！
- Your mama still hasn't missed a shot!
你妈妈还是一枪未失！
Oh, yours is worse,
哦，你的更糟，
[laughter]
哈哈哈
Listen, honey, uh, you know, sometimes
听着，亲爱的，你知道，有时候
when a friend's in a new relationship, you can, uh,
当朋友开始一段新恋情时，你可能会感觉像个电灯泡。
you can feel like a third wheel.
有时候你会觉得自己是个电灯泡。
But, uh, you know, just give her time, and eventually
但，你知道的，给她点时间，最终
she will make shot after shot after shot!
她会投进一个又一个球！
- You can go. - Oh, thank you.
- 你可以走了。- 哦，谢谢你。
[laughter]
[笑声]
Hey, there, honey!
嘿，亲爱的！
Looks like you're really putting the biscuit in the basket.
看起来你真是百发百中啊。
- Not now, Tom, I'm in the zone.
- 现在不行，Tom，我手感正热呢。
- Oh, the zone.
- 哦，手感正热。
I love the zone. [nervous chuckle]
我喜欢这种状态。[紧张的笑]
Zone, zone, zone, zone!
区域，区域，区域，区域！
- Sh!
嘘！
- Zone, zone, zone, zone! - Sh!
区域，区域，区域，区域！嘘！
- Zone, zone, zone, zone! - Boys!
区域，区域，区域，区域！男孩们！
- Okay, Dad. - Zone, zone, zone, zone!
好吧，爸爸。区域，区域，区域，区域！
- You heard the lady. - Get out of her zone.
你听到那位女士的话了。离开她的区域。
[powers off]
[关闭电源]
- Wait, what? What?
等等，什么？什么？
Nooo! [gasping]
不！[喘气]
You!
你！
[laughter] - No, not me.
[笑声] - 不，不是我。
Them!
是他们！
boys: Us?
男孩们: 我们？
- You!
- 你！
They pushed me into the cord.
他们把我推到电线上了。
- Oh, they pushed me into ne-ne-ne-ne-ne.
- 哦，他们把我推到那儿了-那儿-那儿-那儿-那儿。
- [mimicking] - What is all this?
- [模仿] - 这都是怎么回事？
- You're doing all this, I'm-- - Na-na-na-na-na.
- 这都是你干的，我—— - 那-那-那-那-那。
- I love when we get a new game at the store.
- 我喜欢店里新到的游戏。
[laughter]
[笑声]
♪ ♪
[video game sounds]
[电子游戏音效]
[laughter]
[笑声]
[barks]
[吠叫声]
- No, Mae, I understand.
- 不，Mae，我明白。
Well, Mae is with Miles.
嗯，Mae和Miles在一起。
Again.
又一次。
Which means I'm free.
这意味着我自由了。
Again.
又一次。
[laughter]
[笑声]
So do you guys want to do something?
那你们想做点什么吗？
- We are doing something. - I meant with me.
- 我们正在做事情。 - 我是说和我一起。
- Oh, then no.
- 哦，那算了。
- Hey, why don't I just play this Maxbox game with you?
- 嘿，我为什么不和你一起玩这个Maxbox游戏呢？
boys: No! No! No! No!
男孩们: 不！不！不！不！
- See, we're kinda at the final boss,
- 看，我们差不多到最终boss了，
so now's not the best time to add a new pilot.
所以现在不是加入新飞行员的最佳时机。
- Besides, aren't you and Mae supposed to be having
- 而且，你和Mae不是应该在
a chow and chat?
吃饭和聊天吗？
- It's dine and dish, and no.
- 是吃饭和分享，而且不是。
I'm joining in!
我要加入！
- Ugh, fine.
唉，好吧。
Pause.
暂停。
Look, if you're going to join the Quad Squadron,
听着，如果你要加入四重奏中队，
it's very important to stick to our strategy.
坚持我们的策略非常重要。
- We have a very specific nine-part battle plan.
我们有一个非常具体的九部分作战计划。
- I have it written on my leg if you forget anything.
如果你们忘了什么，我腿上写着呢。
- Step one, we fly in slow and tight to avoid their radar.
第一步，我们缓慢紧密地飞行以避开他们的雷达。
- Step two-- - Unpause.
第二步——
boys: Wait!
等等！
- There's the enemy! I'm going in!
- 敌人出现了！我要上了！
- No, that's not the enemy! - That's us!
- 不，那不是敌人！ - 那是我们！
- Read my leg!
- 看我腿上的字！
[laughter]
[笑声]
[video game sounds]
[电子游戏音效]
- [gasps]
- [吸气声]
- That's a short game. - I never loved you!
- 这游戏真短。 - 我从未爱过你！
- Is this because Mae canceled your snack and snark?
- 是因为Mae取消了你的零食和嘲讽吗？
- It's gobble and gossip.
- 是狼吞虎咽和八卦。
- It's dine and dish!
- 是吃饭和爆料！
And no, she did not cancel.
没有，她没有取消。
She just keeps turning all of our Dawn/Mae stuff
她只是把我们和道恩的活动都变成了道恩/梅/迈尔斯的三人行。
into Dawn/Mae/Miles stuff.
啊。
- Ahh. - Miles.
迈尔斯。
- The third wheel blues.
电灯泡的忧伤。
- I mean, I'm glad she's happy, but...
我是说，她开心我也高兴，但……
what am I gonna do, try to keep them apart
难道我要想办法拆散他们，好让我跟她一起玩吗？
so I can hang out with her?
听着，我做不到。
Look, I can't do that.
来吧，我们还是玩游戏吧。
Here, let's just play the game.
不！
- No!
[laughter]
[笑声]
- What Nicky's trying to say is...
Nicky想说的是...
why can't you do that?
你为什么不能那样做？
Nobody enjoys being a third wheel.
没有人喜欢当电灯泡。
- You're right!
你说得对！
I think it's time to get rid of that third wheel.
我想是时候摆脱那个电灯泡了。
- Aren't you the third wheel?
你不是电灯泡吗？
- No, it's Miles! Miles is the third wheel!
不，是Miles！Miles才是电灯泡！
[laughter]
[笑声]
And you guys are gonna help me get rid of him.
你们会帮我摆脱他。
- Um, why would we do that?
- 呃，我们为什么要这么做？
- Because if you don't, your little Quad Squadron
- 因为如果你不这么做，你的小四人组
is going to get a fourth wheel.
就要变成五人组了。
boys: [gasping] No!
男孩们: [吸气声] 不！
[laughter]
[笑声]
- Then it looks like "Operation: Everybody Loses a Wheel" is on.
- 那么看来“大家都少一个轮子”行动开始了。
[laughter]
[笑声]
[barks]
[吠叫声]
[laughter]
[笑声]
♪ ♪
[laughter]
[笑声]
- Oh, yes! Boom!
哦，是的！嘭！
High score!
高分！
- Congratulations, hon.
恭喜你，亲爱的。
- What? You're--
什么？你——
You're not mad that I broke your record?
你不生气我打破了你的记录吗？
- Not at all. Hey, you're better than me
一点也不。嘿，你在这游戏上比我强，我完全没问题。
at this game, and I am fine with it.
哦，好吧。
- Oh, well. - [giggling]
[咯咯笑]
[mimicking] You're not mad that I broke your record.
[模仿] 你没生气我打破了你的记录。
[laughter]
[笑声]
[machine beeping]
[机器哔哔声]
- Okay.
好的。
Time to separate my best friend from her boyfriend.
是时候把我的好朋友和她男朋友分开了。
Hey, Mae, there you are!
嘿，Mae，你在这儿！
Oh, we need to talk.
哦，我们需要谈谈。
Alone. It's an emergency.
单独谈。这是紧急情况。
Would you excuse us?
你能回避一下吗？
[laughter]
[笑声]
- Okay.
好吧。
- What's the emergency?
什么紧急情况？
- It's a fashion emergency.
是时尚紧急情况。
- You look fine-- - No!
你看起来很好--
You. Your socks. They don't go with your outfit!
不！
Here, switch socks with me before Miles notices.
你。你的袜子。它们和你的衣服不搭！
- Switching socks is not a thing.
来，趁迈尔斯没注意到，跟我换袜子。
- Then let's make it a thing.
换袜子不是个事儿。
boys: Hey, Miles!
那我们就让它成为个事儿。
- What are you doing here?
嘿，迈尔斯！
- Just hanging out with Mae.
- 只是和Mae一起闲逛。
boys: Dude!
男孩们: 伙计！
- What?
- 怎么了？
- That's every day this week!
- 这已经是这周每天的事了！
- Yeah.
- 是啊。
- Just saying,
- 只是说说，
if I had fries every day,
如果我每天都吃薯条，
I'd get sick of them.
我会吃腻的。
- I'm not sick of her.
- 我对她可没腻。
- But how can you be sure she's not sick of you?
- 但你怎能确定她没对你腻呢？
- What are you talking about?
- 你在说什么？
- We're talking about girl stuff.
- 我们在聊女生的事。
- And we live with a girl,
- 而且我们和一个女生住在一起，
so we know girl stuff.
- 所以我们懂女生的事。
- If she sees too much of you,
- 如果她见你太多，
she's gonna get tired of you.
- 她会对你感到厌烦的。
- Yeah, Dawn see us every day and she can't stand us.
- 是啊，Dawn每天都看到我们，她已经受不了我们了。
- Ugh, your socks are itchy.
- 呃，你的袜子很痒。
- Oh, but they look good. Isn't that all that matters?
- 哦，但它们看起来不错。这不就是最重要的吗？
[laughter]
[笑声]
Oh!
哦！
You know what you need?
你知道你需要什么吗？
Some french fries.
一些炸薯条。
- No, thanks. I just had some.
- 不了，谢谢。我刚吃过一些。
- You're--get-- get some more!
- 你得——再拿点！
- I don't want more.
- 我不想再吃了。
- Yes, you do. - No, I don't.
- 是的，你想。- 不，我不想。
- You're getting more.
- 你再去拿点。
- But I don't want Mae to get tired of me.
- 但我不想让Mae厌倦我。
This is bad. - Don't worry.
这可不好。- 别担心。
I'm sure a solution will present itself any second now.
我确信解决方案马上就会出现。
- Hey, Nicky!
嘿，尼基！
Mae wants an order of onion rings.
梅想要一份洋葱圈。
- Onion rings?
洋葱圈？
That's weird.
这很奇怪。
Mae never orders onion rings.
梅从不点洋葱圈。
- Yeah,
是啊，
she always orders fries.
她总是点薯条。
- Well, she just told me she's had fries every day
嗯，她刚刚告诉我她这周每天都吃薯条，
this week and she's absolutely sick of them.
她已经完全吃腻了。
Good thing you're not a fry.
还好你不是薯条。
[laughter]
[笑声]
Anyway, now she wants onion rings.
总之，现在她想要洋葱圈。
- Bad news, we're all out of onion rings.
- 坏消息，我们的洋葱圈卖完了。
- Ah! - Oh, no!
- 啊！ - 哦，不！
That's just gonna make her want them even more.
那只会让她更想要洋葱圈。
- Oh, it's gonna be fine, just give her these fries.
- 哦，没事的，给她这些薯条。
She never gets tired of fries, right, buddy?
她从不对薯条厌倦，对吧，伙计？
- I got your fries!
- 我拿到你的薯条了！
- I don't want fries!
- 我不要薯条！
- She doesn't want fries?
她不想要薯条吗？
What do I do?
我该怎么办？
- Make yourself unavailable
让自己变得不可得
and she'll want you even more.
她就会更想要你。
- But I am available.
但我现在有空。
- Not if you're hanging with us.
如果你和我们在一起就不会了。
- You guys would do that for me?
你们会为我这么做吗？
boys: Dude!
哥们！
- Yummy, yummy, yummy!
真好吃，真好吃！
- Seriously, I can't even look at those fries.
说真的，我连看都不想看那些薯条。
- Hey, Mae, I know we're supposed to hang, but...
嘿，梅，我知道我们约好一起玩，但是...
I'm unavailable. Bye!
我没空。再见！
Nice socks, Dawn.
袜子不错，唐。
- What just happened?
刚刚发生了什么？
- I don't know, but I guess that means
我不知道，但我想这意味着
you're free for the rest of the day.
你今天剩下的时间都空闲了。
So what do you want to do?
那么你想做什么？
- Why doesn't Miles want to hang out with me?
为什么迈尔斯不想和我一起玩？
- Oh, look, I think you're focusing on the wrong thing.
哦，看，我觉得你关注错了事情。
The important this is-- I want to hang out with you.
重要的是——我想和你一起玩。
- He said he liked your socks.
- 他说他喜欢你的袜子。
Even though they were my socks.
尽管那是我借给你的袜子。
- Look, forget the socks.
- 听着，忘了袜子的事吧。
- When I was wearing them, he didn't even notice.
- 我穿着它们的时候，他甚至都没注意到。
I've got no socks appeal.
我没有袜子魅力。
- Well, here's something to take your mind off it.
- 好吧，这里有件事可以让你分心。
How about a little dine and dish?
来个边吃边聊怎么样？
So you've got your dine,
所以你有吃的，
now do you have anything to dish?
现在你有什么要聊的吗？
- I do. - Then go ahead!
- 我有。 - 那就说吧！
- [sniffles] I miss him so much!
- [抽泣] 我好想他！
♪ ♪
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
- ♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪
- Okay, Mae. Here's our next Fantasy Fashion scenario.
- 好的，Mae。接下来是我们的下一个幻想时尚场景。
You're going to a swanky pool party at The Weeknd's
你要去The Weeknd的周末豪华泳池派对。
on a weekend. What do you wear?
你会穿什么？
- Will Miles be there? - No.
- Miles会去吗？ - 不会。
- What difference does it make?
- 那有什么关系？
- Come on, Mae, it's like you're not even trying.
- 拜托，Mae，你好像根本没在努力。
- What makes you say that?
- 你为什么这么说？
[laughter]
笑声
- Do you really want to end the game with zero points?
- 你真的想以零分结束游戏吗？
- Yes! I like that zero!
- 是的！我喜欢那个零！
It reminds me of Miles' cute, round head.
它让我想起了迈尔斯那可爱的圆脑袋。
- [sighs]
- 叹气
Ricky! Listen, Mae is really miserable.
瑞奇！听着，梅真的很痛苦。
I think I made a big mistake.
我想我犯了个大错误。
Look, we have to get Mae and Miles back together again.
看，我们得让梅和迈尔斯重新在一起。
- But what if we don't want to?
- 但如果我们不想呢？
- You have to.
- 你必须这么做。
- Okay, I understand that.
好的，我明白这一点。
But what if we don't want to?
但如果我们不想这样做呢？
- [sighs]
叹气
Look, just let me talk to Miles.
听着，让我和Miles谈谈。
- Uh, you can't,
呃，你不能，
he's not available at the moment.
他现在没空。
- Well, where is he?
那么，他在哪里？
- He's with Millie. both: Shh!
他和Millie在一起。嘘！
- Millie?
Millie？
- Yeah, Millie.
是的，Millie。
both: Shh!
嘘！
- Uh, sorry, Dawn. Gotta go!
呃，对不起，Dawn。得走了！
- What? Ugh.
什么？呃。
I can't believe Miles is with another girl.
我真不敢相信Miles和另一个女孩在一起。
- So you guys ready to take flight
所以你们准备好和我们的老朋友Millie一起起飞了吗？
in good old Millie?
男孩们：耶！
boys: Yeah!
[笑声]
[laughter]
这...
- This...
是...
is...
太棒了！
awesome!
[laughter]
（笑声）
- I can't believe Miles' dad is a pilot.
我真不敢相信迈尔斯他爸是飞行员。
- I don't know, guys.
我不知道，伙计们。
It feels wrong...
这感觉不对...
keeping Mae and Miles apart
只是因为我们想玩
just because we wanna play
他爸的飞行模拟器
in his dad's flight simulator.
就把梅和迈尔斯分开。
- Well, when you say it like that,
好吧，你这么一说，
it makes us sound horrible.
我们听起来很糟糕。
- Then let's not say it like that anymore.
那就别再那样说了。
both: Roger that.
收到。
boys: Whoo!
哇！
- [chuckles] That was so much fun.
真是太好玩了。
- Even the crashing is fun.
就连坠机也很有趣。
- Yeah. - Good thing,
是啊。
'cause crashing is all we do.
还好，因为我们只会坠机。
[laughter]
哈哈哈！
boys: Uh-oh!
哎呀！
[laughter]
哈哈哈！
- Let me handle this.
让我来处理这件事。
Nut?
坚果？
- No, I have to talk to Miles.
不，我得和迈尔斯谈谈。
- Nut? That's how you handle this?
坚果？这就是你处理的方式？
- Well, I wasn't gonna give her my raisins.
好吧，我可没打算给她我的葡萄干。
- I'm not interested in your snacks!
我对你的零食没兴趣！
Miles needs to forget about Millie and get back with Mae.
迈尔斯需要忘记米莉，和梅重归于好。
Preferably without Mae knowing that I was the one
最好是在梅不知道是我一开始让他们分手的情况下。
that drove them apart in the first place.
那他在哪儿？
So where is he?
好吧，这是真相。
- All right, here's the truth.
- 好吧，这是真相。
Miles just took off.
- Miles刚刚离开了。
- With Millie?
- 和Millie一起？
- Yeah. He loves that Millie.
- 是的。他爱那个Millie。
- Love?
- 爱？
I can't believe Miles could do that to Mae.
我无法相信Miles会这样对Mae。
I have to find Miles and Millie, and fix this.
我必须找到Miles和Millie，并解决这个问题。
- She knows Millie is in there, right?
- 她知道Millie在里面，对吧？
- You don't think Dawn thinks Millie's an actual girl, do you?
- 你不会认为Dawn真的把Millie当成一个真正的女孩吧？
both: Nah.
两人：不会。
[laughter]
[笑声]
♪ ♪
- Come on, Langer, faster! I gotta get my high score back.
- 快点，Langer，再快点！我得把我的高分夺回来。
- I don't think this is in my job description, Mr. Harper.
- 我觉得这不在我的工作职责里，Harper先生。
- Neither is complaining. Just feed me the rock!
- 抱怨也不在。快把球给我！
- Really, Tom?
- 真的吗，Tom？
[laughs] I can't believe you would cheat
[笑] 我真不敢相信你会为了打败我的高分而作弊。
just to beat my high score.
- Harper先生让我这么做的！ - [嗤之以鼻]
- Mr. Harper made me do it! - [scoffs]
- 谢谢你，Langer。
- Thank you, Langer.
- 是的，好吧，你抓到我了。 - 嗯哼。
Yes, okay, you caught me. - Uh-huh.
是的，好吧，你抓到我了。
- I'm a cheater, but for a good reason!
嗯哼。
You're so much better than me.
我是个作弊者，但有个好理由！
- Oh, honey, I'm so sorry...
你比我强太多了。
for being so good. [laughs]
哦，亲爱的，我很抱歉...
- Not as good as this kid.
因为我太优秀了。
- Whoa. [game dinging]
没有这孩子那么好。
She's better than both of us.
哇。
Trip me.
她比我们俩都强。
- [clears throat]
绊倒我。
- Okay, I just gotta go over here for a second.
好的，我需要过去一下。
Oh! Oh! Oh! - Oh, dear!
哦！哦！哦！
- Oh! Oh! - Oh.
哦，天哪！
Oh! Oh! - Oh!
哦！哦！
- What the heck?
哦！
- Oh, honey, we are so sorry.
这是怎么回事？
- Yes, but since it's broken anyway,
哦，亲爱的，我们非常抱歉。
you should probably just go.
是的，但既然已经坏了，
- [chuckles]
你或许应该离开。
- Or...
或者...
you could plug it back in.
你可以重新插上电源。
[laughter]
[笑声]
- Yes, sir.
是的，先生。
- And let my daughter play
让我女儿继续玩
till she gets the high score.
直到她得到最高分。
- Of course, sir. - [chuckles]
当然，先生。
Plug it in, plug it in, plug it in...
插上电源，插上电源，插上电源...
- Oh, right. - Plug it in, plug it in,
哦，对了。
plug it in, plug it in!
插上电源，插上电源，插上电源，插上电源！
- Oh, hey, you're Millie, right?
哦，嘿，你是米莉，对吧？
- Yeah.
是的。
- Hello, Millie.
你好，米莉。
- Oh, I know you.
哦，我认识你。
- You don't say.
你不说。
- You're the Edgewood Buffalo's goal keeper, right?
你是Edgewood Buffalo队的守门员，对吧？
- Yeah, what's it to you?
是的，那又怎样？
- You're good.
你很厉害。
- Thank you!
谢谢！
Don't try to sweet-talk me, Millie.
别想用甜言蜜语哄我，米莉。
I saw on your FaceShack page that you just checked in here.
我在你的FaceShack页面上看到你刚签到在这里。
And it also said that you and Miles are "friends."
So where is he?
And why are you trying to steal my BFF's BF, GF?
- What? I don't like Miles!
I'm only FaceShack friends with him
because his mom is my dentist.
- Oh! [giggles]
Your dentist.
Oh, sorry. Wrong Millie.
Don't forget to floss.
- Wait.
等等。
I thought Miles was with Mae.
我以为Miles和Mae在一起。
- He is. But apparently he took off
他是和Mae在一起。但显然他今天早些时候和某个“Millie”跑了。
with some "Millie" earlier today.
真的吗？
- Really?
你的闺蜜的男朋友就这样随随便便地和其他Millie跑了？
Your BFF's BF is running around
是啊！
with some other Millie all willy-nilly?
没有男朋友应该这样对待他们的女朋友。
- Yeah!
你说得对。
- No BF should treat their GF like that.
作为那个女朋友的闺蜜，
- You're right.
我需要尽快找到那个男朋友。
And as that GF's BFF,
作为那个女朋友的闺蜜，
I need to find that BF ASAP
我需要尽快找到那个男朋友
and teach that D-O-G some R-E-S-P-E-C-T.
并教那只狗学会尊重。
- W-O-R-D.
说得好。
[laughter]
[笑声]
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
[all screaming, alarm blaring]
[所有人尖叫，警报响起]
[alarm blaring]
[警报响起]
[mechanical whirring]
[机械的嗡嗡声]
- We are so not good at this.
我们在这方面真的很不擅长。
- Don't worry.
别担心。
Even my dad crashes sometimes.
即使我爸爸有时也会坠机。
- Really? - No.
真的吗？
I'm gonna go get us some more snacks.
我去给咱们再拿点零食。
[laughter]
笑声
- You know what I love most about this?
你知道我最喜欢这里什么吗？
- All these cool knobs and switches?
所有这些酷炫的旋钮和开关？
[clattering]
咔嗒声
- May be why we keep crashing.
可能就是我们一直坠机的原因。
- No!
不！
What I love is that Dawn can't ruin this for us.
我最喜欢的是，Dawn无法破坏我们的这份美好。
- Oh, hello, Miles.
- 哦，你好，Miles。
♪ ♪
[door slams]
[门砰的一声关上]
- Hey, Dawn.
- 嘿，Dawn。
Why are you looking at me like you want to hurt me?
你为什么这样看着我，好像你想伤害我？
- Mae really liked you.
- Mae真的很喜欢你。
And I thought you really liked her.
我以为你真的很喜欢她。
- I do.
- 我是喜欢她。
- Then why are you spending
- 那你为什么
all your time with Millie?
把所有时间都花在米莉身上？
- Because your brothers told me
- 因为你的兄弟们告诉我
Millie would keep my mind off Mae.
米莉能让我不去想梅。
- My brothers!
- 我的兄弟们！
Can't believe they were in on this.
真不敢相信他们也参与了这件事。
- In on it?
- 参与了？
They love Millie more than I do.
他们爱米莉胜过我爱她。
- What? - Yeah.
- 什么？ - 是啊。
They're in there with her right now.
他们现在正和她在一起。
- What? [laughter]
什么？[笑声]
- See? Isn't Millie great?
看吧？米莉是不是很棒？
- What?
什么？
[laughter]
[笑声]
[pounding on door]
[敲门声]
- [gasps] Uh, guys?
哎，伙计们？
We got a problem.
我们有个问题。
- Air speed is fine.
空速没问题。
All gauges normal.
所有仪表正常。
- No, we have a real problem.
不，我们有个真正的问题。
- You kept Mae and Miles apart for a flight simulator?
- 你让Mae和Miles在飞行模拟器上分开操作？
- She's onto us. What are we gonna do?
- 她已经察觉到我们了。我们该怎么办？
- Let's get outta here!
- 我们快离开这里！
[laughter]
- [笑声]
- Dicky, this thing doesn't really fly.
- Dicky，这东西根本飞不起来。
- [gasps] Doesn't matter. She's onto us.
- [吸气声] 无所谓了。她已经察觉到我们了。
- You said that already! - No!
- 你已经说过了！ - 不！
She's onto us.
- 她已经察觉到我们了。
[all screaming]
- [所有人尖叫]
- Get rid of her!
- 把她赶走！
- It's gonna take more than that.
- 这还不够。
Or that!
或者那个也不行！
[laughter]
[笑声]
Okay, okay. That almost got me.
好吧，好吧。那差点让我上当。
- I'll take care of this.
- 我来处理这件事。
[mechanical whirring]
[机械的嗡嗡声]
Ugh! I can't shake her!
呃！我甩不掉她！
- I can't believe you guys could be so selfish.
- 真不敢相信你们能这么自私。
- Don't blame us!
- 别怪我们！
Keeping Mae and Miles apart
让Mae和Miles分开
was all your idea.
都是你的主意。
- But I realized I was wrong and tried to fix it.
但我意识到我错了，并试图改正。
- By telling Mae the truth?
通过告诉Mae真相？
- Well, no, but--
嗯，不是，但是--
- Now! She's distracted!
现在！她分心了！
- We did it!
我们做到了！
[alarm blaring] - We're going down!
我们正在下降！
[all screaming]
所有人尖叫
[tires squeak]
轮胎吱吱作响
[tone dinging]
音调叮叮作响
- We did it! We landed the plane.
- 我们做到了！我们成功降落了飞机。
- But what about Dawn?
- 但是Dawn怎么办？
We can't just leave her up there.
我们不能就这样把她留在上面。
- She's not up there, Dicky.
- 她不在上面，Dicky。
- Yes, I am!
- 不，我在！
[all screaming]
[所有人尖叫]
- Okay, fine, we were all selfish
- 好吧，好吧，我们都自私了
and none of us were totally truthful.
而且我们都没有完全说实话。
- But if you would just
- 但如果你能
fly this thing, you'd understand.
驾驶这东西，你就会明白。
- I doubt it. I mean, what's so great
我怀疑。我的意思是，一架没有翅膀的大飞机有什么好的？
about a big plane with no wings?
这...
This...
太...
is...
棒了！[笑]
awesome! [laughs]
你们是对的。
You guys were right.
这一切都值得。
This was totally worth it.
- 是吗？- 啊！
- Was it? - Ah!
梅，你在这里干什么？
- Mae, what are you doing here?
- 迈尔斯发短信给我说有些奇怪的事情在发生。
- Miles texted me that something weird was going on.
他是对的。我真不敢相信你会这样对我。
And he was right.
而且他说得对。
I can't believe you'd do this to me.
我真不敢相信你会这样对我。
- And I can't believe you guys would do this to me.
- 我真不敢相信你们会这样对我。
- Dude...
- 伙计...
- Dude.
- 伙计。
- Mm. Dude.
- 嗯。伙计。
- Dude.
- 伙计。
- Dude?
- 伙计？
- Dude.
- 伙计。
[laughter]
[笑声]
- That's it?
就这样？
You're all made up?
你们都准备好了？
- Yeah. We're dudes.
是啊，我们是哥们。
- Ugh. I don't get boys sometimes.
唉，有时候我真的搞不懂男生。
[laughter]
（笑声）
Dude?
哥们？
- Girl.
女孩。
- Right.
对。
Look, Mae, I really am sorry.
听着，Mae，我真的很抱歉。
I was a jerk.
我那时是个混蛋。
I just didn't want to lose you
我只是不想失去你
'cause you were spending all your time with Miles,
因为你把所有时间都花在Miles身上，
so I did something really dumb;
所以我做了件真的很蠢的事；
I got my brothers involved.
我让我兄弟们掺和进来了。
- I want to be mad at you, I really do,
- 我想对你生气，我真的想，
but all you really wanted to do was spend time with me,
但你真正想要的只是和我共度时光，
which I get, 'cause I'm awesome.
我理解，因为我太棒了。
- [chuckles]
- [轻笑]
Look, I really am sorry. - Me too.
听着，我真的真的很抱歉。 - 我也是。
And I promise I'll always make time for you.
我保证我会永远为你腾出时间。
- And I promise I will never try to drive you
and Miles apart again.
- Just one question:
is Millie really all that?
- Girl...
- Dude!
[laughter]
- They're never coming out, are they?
boys: Dude!
both: Girl!
[engines whooshing]
[引擎呼啸声]
[laughter]
[笑声]
♪♪
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
- ♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪
[whistling]
[口哨声]
♪ ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
- ♪ 耶！ ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 耶！ ♪